<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Euro2012Planner</string>
    <string name="news_title">News Channel</string>
    <string name="games_title">Fixtures</string>
    <string name="venues_title">Venues</string>
    <string name="teams_title">Teams</string>
    <string name="refresh_text">Refresh</string>

    <string-array name="groups">
        <item>Group A</item>
        <item>Group B</item>
        <item>Group C</item>
        <item>Group D</item>
        <item>Group E</item>
        <item>Group F</item>
        <item>Group G</item>
        <item>Group H</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="knockout">
        <item>Second Round</item>
        <item>Quarter-Final</item>
        <item>Semi-Final</item>
        <item>FINAL</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="venues">
        <item>Arena Corinthians, São Paulo</item> 		<!-- 0 -->
        <item>Arena das Dunas, Natal</item> 			<!-- 1 -->
        <item>Estádio Castelão, Fortaleza</item>		<!-- 2 -->
        <item>Arena Amazônia, Manaus</item>				<!-- 3 -->
        <item>E. N. Mané Garrincha, Brasília</item>		<!-- 4 -->
        <item>Arena Pernambuco, Recife</item>			<!-- 5 -->
        <item>Arena Fonte Nova, Salvador</item>			<!-- 6 -->
        <item>Arena Pantanal, Cuiabá</item>				<!-- 7 -->
        <item>E. Beira-Rio, Porto Alegre</item>			<!-- 8 -->
        <item>E. do Maracanã, Rio de Janeiro</item>		<!-- 9 -->        
        <item>E. Mineirão, Belo Horizonte</item>		<!-- 10 -->
        <item>Arena da Baixada, Curitiba</item>   		<!-- 11 -->     
    </string-array>

    <!--
         Venues_Short, do not translate!
         should obviously match venues array
    -->
    <string-array name="venues_short">
        <item>spaulo</item>
        <item>natal</item>
        <item>fortaleza</item>
        <item>manaus</item>
        <item>brasilia</item>
        <item>recife</item>
        <item>salvador</item>
        <item>cuiaba</item>
        <item>palegre</item>
        <item>rio</item>
        <item>belohoriz</item>
        <item>curitiba</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="venue_capacities">
        <item>68,000 Capacity</item>
        <item>42,086 Capacity</item>
        <item>64,846 Capacity</item>
        <item>42,374 Capacity</item>
        <item>70,042 Capacity</item>
        <item>46,154 Capacity</item>
        <item>56,000 Capacity</item>
        <item>42,968 Capacity</item>
        <item>51,300 Capacity</item>
        <item>76,935 Capacity</item>
        <item>62,547 Capacity</item>
        <item>43,981 Capacity</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="team_names">
        <item>Brazil</item>
        <item>Croatia</item>
        <item>Mexico</item>
        <item>Cameroon</item>
        <item>Spain</item>
        <item>Netherlands</item>
        <item>Chile</item>
        <item>Australia</item>
        <item>Colombia</item>
        <item>Greece</item>
        <item>Ivory Coast</item>
        <item>Japan</item>
        <item>Uruguay</item>
        <item>Costa Rica</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>Italy</item>
        <item>Switzerland</item>
        <item>Ecuador</item>
        <item>France</item>
        <item>Honduras</item>
        <item>Argentina</item>
        <item>Bos Herz</item>
        <item>Iran</item>
        <item>Nigeria</item>
        <item>Germany</item>
        <item>Portugal</item>
        <item>Ghana</item>
        <item>USA</item>
        <item>Belgium</item>
        <item>Algeria</item>
        <item>Russia</item>
        <item>S Korea</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--
         Team drawables, do not translate!
         should obviously match team array
    -->
    
    <string-array name="team_icon_resource_names">
        <item>brazil</item>
        <item>croatia</item>
        <item>mexico</item>
        <item>cameroon</item>
        <item>spain</item>
        <item>netherlands</item>
        <item>chile</item>
        <item>australia</item>
        <item>colombia</item>
        <item>greece</item>
        <item>ivorycoast</item>
        <item>japan</item>
        <item>uruguay</item>
        <item>costarica</item>
        <item>england</item>
        <item>italy</item>
        <item>switzerland</item>
        <item>ecuador</item>
        <item>france</item>
        <item>honduras</item>
        <item>argentina</item>
        <item>bosniaherz</item>
        <item>iran</item>
        <item>nigeria</item>
        <item>germany</item>
        <item>portugal</item>
        <item>ghana</item>
        <item>unitedstates</item>
        <item>belgium</item>
        <item>algeria</item>
        <item>russia</item>
        <item>southkorea</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="sr_placeholder_names">
        <item>1st Group A</item>
        <item>2nd Group B</item>
        <item>1st Group B</item>
        <item>2nd Group A</item>
        <item>1st Group C</item>
        <item>2nd Group D</item>
        <item>1st Group D</item>
        <item>2nd Group C</item>
        <item>1st Group E</item>
        <item>2nd Group F</item>
        <item>1st Group F</item>
        <item>2nd Group E</item>
        <item>1st Group G</item>
        <item>2nd Group H</item>
        <item>1st Group H</item>
        <item>2nd Group G</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="qf_placeholder_names">
        <item>Winner SR 1</item>
        <item>Winner SR 2</item>
        <item>Winner SR 3</item>
        <item>Winner SR 4</item>
        <item>Winner SR 5</item>
        <item>Winner SR 6</item>
        <item>Winner SR 7</item>
        <item>Winner SR 8</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sf_placeholder_names">
        <item>Winner QF 1</item>
        <item>Winner QF 2</item>
        <item>Winner QF 3</item>
        <item>Winner QF 4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="f_placeholder_names">
        <item>Winner SF 1</item>
        <item>Winner SF 2</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sr_game_titles">
        <item>SR1</item>
        <item>SR2</item>
        <item>SR3</item>
        <item>SR4</item>
        <item>SR5</item>
        <item>SR6</item>
        <item>SR7</item>
        <item>SR8</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="qf_game_titles">
        <item>QF1</item>
        <item>QF2</item>
        <item>QF3</item>
        <item>QF4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sf_game_titles">
        <item>SF1</item>
        <item>SF2</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="f_game_titles">
        <item>F</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="menuGames">Games</string>
    <string name="menuVenues">Venues</string>
    <string name="menuTeams">Teams</string>
    <string name="menuNews">News</string>
    <string name="loadingNews">Loading News&#8230;</string>
    <string name="homeButton">Home Button</string>

    <string name="cdVenueDesc">Venues</string>

    <string name="played_hdr">P</string>
    <string name="goals_for_hdr">F</string>
    <string name="goals_against_hdr">A</string>
    <string name="points_hdr">Pts</string>

    <string name="jersey_hdr">#</string>
    <string name="player_hdr">Player</string>
    <string name="age_hdr">Age</string>
    <string name="server_error_body">Error in handling squad data. Please try again later.</string>

    <string name="cdIcon">Icon</string>

    <string name="fixtureIconHomeCD">Home Team Icon</string>
    <string name="fixtureIconAwayCD">Away Team Icon</string>

    <string name="scoreSeperator"> - </string>
    <string name="scoreSeperatorUnplayed"> v </string>

    <string name="daysToGo">%d days to go!</string>
    <string name="oneDayToGo">One day to go!</string>

    <string name="aboutMenu">About</string>

    <string name="teamsIconCD">Team Icon</string>
    <string name="feedLoadingError">Unable to load news. Please check your internet connection.</string>
    <!-- Do not translate -->
    <string name="adsId">4028cba631d63df10131e1d3818b00cc</string>
    
    <!-- News Ticker -->
    <string name="ticker_text">FIFA News Loading.... Touch for Full Index!</string>
    <string name="loadingFeedError">News Channel Temporarily Unavailable.</string>
    <string name="fifa_feed_lead">FIFA.com News &#8230;</string>
    <string name="fifa_feed_tail">*END OF FEED* &#8230;</string>

    <string name="aboutHeader">About</string>
    <string name="aboutText">Euro 2012 Planner Application developed by John
        O\'Halloran and Stephen Roberts (@steprobe) &#169; 2012. Team write ups by Mark O\'Reilly.
        \n\n
        Credits for stadium images:\n\n
        http://www.euro2012.uke.gov.pl/public/Page/Stadiums/Poznan/Rys0.jpg\n\n
        http://pics.livejournal.com/tov_tob/pic/005xw8b3\n\n
        http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Stadion_Narodowy_w_Warszawie_20120422.jpg\n\n
        http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:PGE_Arena.jpeg\n\n
        http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Stadion_Wroclaw_z_lotu_ptaka.jpg\n\n
        http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Donezk_Donbass_Arena_01.JPG\n\n
        http://www.soccerfansnetwork.com/\n\n
        http://www.lenam-travel.co.uk/\n\n
        http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Tango_12_match_ball_of_UEFA_EURO_2012.png\n\n
        Come on you boys in green!!\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="errorHeader">Error</string>
    <string name="loadingTournError">Unable to load latest tournament data. Data may be out of date.</string>
    <string name="loadingSquadError">Unable to load latest squad data. Sqauds may be out of date.</string>
    <string name="loadingResults">Loading latest fixtures and results&#8230;</string>
    <string name="loadingSquads">Loading latest squad data&#8230;</string>

    <array name="adKeywords">
        <item>World Cup 2014</item>
        <item>Football</item>
        <item>Sport</item>
        <item>Soccer</item>
        <item>Brazil</item>
        <item>South America</item>
        <item>Travel</item>
        <item>futbol</item>
        <item>eurocopa</item>
    </array>

    <!-- Strings for squad tabs -->
    <string name="squadHeader">Squad</string>
    <string name="squadProspects">Prediction</string>
    <string name="squadStarPlayer">Star Player</string>

    <string name="prediction">Prediction:</string>

    <!--  Write Ups -->
    <string name="writeupNotFound">Write up not available</string>
    <string name="starPlayerWriteupNotFound">Star Player Write up not available</string>
    <string name="predictionNotFound">Not available</string>
    <string name="nameNotFound">Not available</string>

    <!--  Below here not in Spanish -->

    <string name="writeup0">Hosts and five-time winners Brazil rightly go into the tournament as one of the favourites. With outstanding talents throughout the team and with an efficiency drilled by caoch Scolari, Brazil are capable of beating the best. The only worry may be that automatic qualification may mean the team will lack that competitive edge. However, it would be brave to bet against them especially with home advantage.</string>
    <string name="prediction0">The twelfth man will be just enough to see Brazil edge past the others to win the World Cup on home soil.</string>
    <string name="starman0">So good they only named him once! Barcelona\'s Neymar is coming-of-age at the perfect time for this tournament. The hopes and prayers of his nation will be on his shoulders and he could achieve God-like status if he influences the team to a successful home World Cup.</string>
    <string name="starmanname0">Neymar</string>

    <string name="writeup1">With some excellent players and a strategic manager, Croatia should be going into this tournament full of confidence. However, their qualifying campaign was lackluster and had they not been fortuitous enough to draw Iceland in the qualifiers they may well have been watching this tournament from a distance. With the players art their disposal, especially in midfield, they may cause problems even to the bigger teams. But they will need things to really click into place for them to progress beyond the second round.</string>
    <string name="prediction1">Second round exit</string>
    <string name="starman1">The Real Madrid player is one of the best passers in world football and is the centre of all things that are good for Croatia. If he gets time and space he can cause real damage.</string>
    <string name="starmanname1">Luka Modrić</string>
    
    <string name="writeup2">With recent managerial and playing-system changes, Mexico aren\'t arriving to the tournament in the settled state that would be preferred. They have at their disposal a number of talented players with plenty of pace and trickery. But given their tough group they will have to find something extra to progress very far.</string>
    <string name="prediction2">Going home early</string>
    <string name="starman2">Although struggling to stake out a first team place at club Manchester United, Hernandez has skill and pace to burnf. He will need to be at his lethal best for Mexico to make any headlines.</string>
    <string name="starmanname2">Javier Hernández</string>

    <string name="writeup3">One of the current forces of African football, Cameroon will be tricky opponents and will be unfazed by the high Brazilian temperatures. They have a wealth of pace, power and fitness but will need calm heads and strong leadership to make any waves.</string>
    <string name="prediction3">Group exit</string>
    <string name="starman3">Samuel Eto\'o, the captain and leader, will need to inspire those around him to perform with the perfect balance of controlled agression to navigate a difficult group.</string>
    <string name="starmanname3">Samuel Eto\'o</string>
    
    <string name="writeup4">The World Cup and Europen Cup holders go in to the tournament as one of favourites. The team largely remains the same, which is good from the point of view of stability, but perhaps a little bit worrying in terms of the ageing profile. Bayern Munich handed a blueprint to combat their short-passing style in their Champions League victory over Barcelona. Adding Brazil\'s comfotable federation cup final victory over the national team has lead some to conclude that the golden era for Spain is drawing to a close. This seems somewhat premature and Spain will be there right to the end.</string>
    <string name="prediction4">Semi finalists</string>
    <string name="starman4">Delivers on the biggest occasions and will have to do so again if Spain are the conquer the other giants and lift the cup.</string>
    <string name="starmanname4">Andrés Iniesta</string>
    
    <string name="writeup5">With a mouth-watering clash with Spain the pick of the early fixtures, this Dutch side has an interesting mix of youth and experience that will be very interesting to watch. Unfortunately, there is always the cloud of egos and infighting that often disrupts the Dutch in the big events. If they can avoid that, they can go far.</string>
    <string name="prediction5">Quarter finals</string>
    <string name="starman5">It\'s hard to believe that Arjen Robben will only be 30 years old at this tournament. It seems like he has been playing forever. He contributes massively to Bayern winning the Champions League and will be massive for the Netherlands in Brazil.</string>
    <string name="starmanname5">Arjen Robben</string>
    
    <string name="writeup6">Chile will feal resonably at home in Brazil and will play without any fear as expectation is not very high on them in a group with two of the giants of European football. Neither Spain nor The Netherlands will look forward to playing Chile and I can forsee them getting a result from one of those games.</string>
    <string name="prediction6">Brave performances but ultimately a group stage exit.</string>
    <string name="starman6">The Juventus star is one of the most exciting talents in world football with lively link up play and good finishing on his resume.</string>
    <string name="starmanname6">Arturo Vidal</string>
    
    <string name="writeup7">From Australia\'s point of view, this is a group of death. Their stars are passed their prime and their young talent is good but not superb. They will do well if they avoid embarrassment in one of the toughest groups of the tournament.</string>
    <string name="prediction7">First flight home</string>
    <string name="starman7">The Crystal Palace captain is a gritty performer and will have to inspire this throughout the team for Australia not to go home blushing.</string>
    <string name="starmanname7">Mile Jedinak</string>
    
    <string name="writeup8">Colombia looked like an assured team in qualifying and haven been given a group of which most other teams are jealous this could be the year for Colombia to finally fulfil their much touted ambitions. It will be interesting to see how their team fares against highly drilled European outfits (assuming they get that far) but they will definitley be a team to watch in Brazil.</string>
    <string name="prediction8">Quarter finals with a chance to go further.</string>
    <string name="starman8">A sublime attacking talent, he could be one of the heroes of the cup.</string>
    <string name="starmanname8">Radamel Falcao</string>
    
    <string name="writeup9">The Greeks boast a very mean defence and rigit organisation that makes them difficult for any team to beat. On the other side, they are lacking the flair of the serious contenders in this tournament.</string>
    <string name="prediction9">Group stage exit</string>
    <string name="starman9">A top-class centre forward but will require his teammates to provide the service and this may be the problem.</string>
    <string name="starmanname9">Konstantinos Mitroglou</string>
    
    <string name="writeup10">The highest ranked African team and definietely a team to watch in this tournament. They will fancy their chances of progression from this group and few teams will fancy meeting them beyond that stage. With an extremely fit and strong team, the grueling schedule of games will suit them better than most. Likely to cause an upset along the way and make a few headlines.</string>
    <string name="prediction10">Quarter Finals</string>
    <string name="starman10">Man City\'s midfield engine is one of the finest players gracing the tournament and will help his team to some memorable results.</string>
    <string name="starmanname10">Yaya Toure</string>
    
    <string name="writeup11">Japan have undoubted (if underrated) talent up front but lack the resiliance in defence that is needed to pose a serious threat of qualifying from this group. They are lightly to cause their opponents problems and show some flashed of brilliance but ultimately this is unlikely to be a trip for the Blue Samurai to remember for too long.</string>
    <string name="prediction11">Moments of beautiful football but ultimately an early flight home.</string>
    <string name="starman11">Formerly one fo the finest players in the Budesliga, Kagawa gets very limited game time at Manchester United. Will feel he has a point to prove in Brazil.</string>
    <string name="starmanname11">Shinji Kagawa</string>
    
    <string name="writeup12">With a fearsome attacking line, defenders will be having nightmares about going toe-to-toe with Uruguay. Luis Suarez is fast becoming one of the best strikers in the world and if his current form continues he looks capable of beating a team on his own. Uruguay will be looking to top the group and could definitely upset some big names in this tournament.</string>
    <string name="prediction12">Quarter finals would seem very possible and I wouldn\'t bet against seeing them in the semis either.</string>
    <string name="starman12">He has everything to be one of the greats of this era. If he can keep his discipline in check he could be making a lot of headlines this summer.</string>
    <string name="starmanname12">Luis Suarez</string>
    
    <string name="writeup13">Costa Rica boast a mean defence and their qualifying record is impressive. However, this is all against teams that could hardly claim to be in football\'s top tier. It will be interesting to see how Costa Rica will cope against stronger footballing nations and whether they can find a few goals to help them challenge for qualification from the group.</string>
    <string name="prediction13">Group stage exit</string>
    <string name="starman13">A quality player who has all the talent but sometimes lacks consistency. Will need a huge tournament to avoid sitting at the bottom of the group after the first three games.</string>
    <string name="starmanname13">Bryan Ruiz</string>
    
    <string name="writeup14">National expectation is low in England for this tournament which is possibly the first time ever in the modern era. A lot of the stars from their golden era are coming into their autumn years and under Roy Hodgson their qualification campaign was quite a conservative affair for the most part. Some recent performances have hinted towards a more expansive style of play but when the tournament pressure arrives it will be surprising if England don\'t focus more of their efforts on not conceding than on anything else.</string>
    <string name="prediction14">Second round seems possible but getting much further would require some excellent performances and a slice of luck.</string>
    <string name="starman14">Having recently exploded onto the national team, this exciting player is capable of being the spark that England require.</string>
    <string name="starmanname14">Andros Townsend</string>
    
    <string name="writeup15">Perennial overachievers in tournament football, you write Italy off at your peril. With an ability to get results that scarcely seem possible and often don\'t seem deserved, Italy could be there right to the end. However, on paper this side just doesn\'t look strong enough to compete. Pirlo is an undoubtedly fine player, but for your playmaker to be 35 years old in such hot conditions, it seems like Italy will struggle against top teams.</string>
    <string name="prediction15">May scrape through the group but going home before the quarter final stage.</string>
    <string name="starman15">Pirlo can single-handedly dismantle teams, as he showed against England in their last tournament meeting. But has he the legs to play this packed schedule in such heat? </string>
    <string name="starmanname15">Andrea Pirlo</string>
     
    <string name="writeup16">Impressive in qualifying and one of the top seeds of the tournament, the credentials of this Swiss team look good on paper. However, it remains to be seen how well they will cope when they are pitted against some of the bigger teams. Expect to see performances full of energy and organisation but their lack of creative flair may prevent them from making a huge impact at the cup.</string>
    <string name="prediction16">Second round but no further.</string>
    <string name="starman16">The Bayern Muncih player combines a low centre of gravity with two-footed trickery that can be a handful for defenders.</string>
    <string name="starmanname16">Xerdan Shaqiri</string>
    
    <string name="writeup17">Not hugely impressive in qualifying, particularly when away from home, there is little to suggest that Ecuador will be doing much more than making up the numbers at World Cup 2014. They have wingers with talent but there are many frailties throughout the team that are likely to get exposed on the biggest stage.</string>
    <string name="prediction17">Early elimination</string>
    <string name="starman17">Undboutedly has the talent to shine at this tournament but could just as easily do nothing to be noticed.</string>
    <string name="starmanname17">Antonio Valencia</string>
    
    <string name="writeup18">Having fought back from the brink of elimination in their qualfier against the Ukraine, France then landed the group that all the bottom seeds were dreaming of. Their team is full of star names and in coach Deschamps they have a man with a chance of keeping balance among the many egos in the squad.</string>
    <string name="prediction18">A lot depends on the desire and harmony in the group, with anything from first round elimination to World Cup winners a possibility. Predicting quarter finals.</string>
    <string name="starman18">Already one of the world\'s best players, Ribery has taken his game to another level over the past couple of years and has become the complete player.</string>
    <string name="starmanname18">Franck Ribéry</string>
    
    <string name="writeup19">Honduras would be happy to come home from this tournament with a win under their belts and would be ecstatic with anything more. The group is kind and they might not get a better opportunity for three World Cup points for some time to come.</string>
    <string name="prediction19">May get that first win but still unlikely to qualify from the group. </string>
    <string name="starman19">Pacy left-back Emilio Izaguirre is a real attacking threat and will need to perform well for Honduras to get the goals and win their nation is dreaming of.</string>
    <string name="starmanname19">Emilio Izaguirre</string>
    
    <string name="writeup20">The era of Maradonna\'s management of the Argentinian side was somewhat of a waste of the talents available but this time out Argentina have a better shot at making a real impact in the tournament. With a wealth of attacking talent and probably the world\'s best player, Argentina are real contenders to win the tournament in the home of their neighbours. The Brazilian public would rather see any other team win so Argentina can expect a hostile reception for the locals - will this distract or galvanise them?</string>
    <string name="prediction20">Anything less than semi-finals would be a shock, but will need nerves of steel to win the tournament. Beaten semi-finalists.</string>
    <string name="starman20">Nominated the World\'s best player for the last four years and boasting a goal scoring record that is bordering on the obscene, it\'s going to take a lot for Messi not to have a huge influence in this tournament.</string>
    <string name="starmanname20">Lionel Messi</string>
    
    <string name="writeup21">A solid team with some world-class players, Bosnia- Hertzegovina could make a name for themselves at their first World Cup. Capable of getting a result against any other team they will be one to watch.</string>
    <string name="prediction21">Provided the occasion doesn\'t get to them, Bosnia-Herzegovina will get out of the group but the dream will end there.</string>
    <string name="starman21">Man City\'s Edin Dzeko scored 10 goals in the qualifying campaign and it will be no surprise if he knocks in a few more in Brazil.</string>
    <string name="starmanname21">Edin Džeko</string>
    
    <string name="writeup22">Iran\'s form-guide won\'t frighten anyone in this tournament, including a 1-0 defeat at the hands of lowly Lebanon. They will be hoping to return from the tournament with their pride intact, which may even be a little to optimistic.</string>
    <string name="prediction22">Second round seems possible but getting much further would require some excellent performances and a slice of luck.</string>
    <string name="starman22">The captain has been a mainstay of the team for a long time and will be hoping to bow out of international football with his head held high.</string>
    <string name="starmanname22">Javan Nekounam</string>
    
    <string name="writeup23">There is no doubting that Nigeria have the pace and athleticism to cause their group opponents problems. Unfortunately they also have a note of turmoil in their organisation and performances can be inconsistent. Could cause an upset if everything lines up properly for them.</string>
    <string name="prediction23">Their game with Boznia- Hertzegovena will be a fascinating one to watch and will likely decide which team progresses. I predict Nigeria to narrowly lose that game and bow out at the group stage.</string>
    <string name="starman23">Blossoming at Chelsea of late, Mickel possesses the ability to control a game and make it look easy.</string>
    <string name="starmanname23">John Obi Mikel</string>
    
    <string name="writeup24">With a starting eleven as good as any in the tournament and a bench that is the envy of most of the world, Germany are incredibly strong contenders at this World Cup. Combining teachnical excellence with elite athleticism, it is going to take a team with doses of talent and organisation to stop the rampaging Germans from going all the way.</string>
    <string name="prediction24">Beaten finalists.</string>
    <string name="starman24">His departure from Real Madrid over the summer was greeted by shock all around the footballing world, having been one of Madrid\'s star performers the previous season.</string>
    <string name="starmanname24">Mesut Özil</string>
    
    <string name="writeup25">A team with many talented individuals that just seem to be lacking a bit of team-spirit. In Ronaldo they have probably the world\'s second-best player and he is capable of glossing over their dificiencies and dragging them to big results (as he notably did in the qualfier play-offs against Sweden).</string>
    <string name="prediction25">Should cruise through the group but may struggle against more complete teams. Quarter finals.</string>
    <string name="starman25">Ronaldo will be keen to establish a case that he is a better player than certain other South American attackers.</string>
    <string name="starmanname25">Christiano Ronaldo</string>
    
    <string name="writeup26">A strong midfield contrasts sharply with Ghana\'s options in defence and attack. They will play some nice football and may nick a goal or two but are unlikely to trouble the European big-boys in their group.</string>
    <string name="prediction26">Group stage exit</string>
    <string name="starman26">Though a fading power at club level, Essien is still a huge player for the national team.</string>
    <string name="starmanname26">Michael Essien</string>
    
    <string name="writeup27">For all the stubbornness and strong organisation in this US team, there is a conspicuous lack of world class players on the team sheet that will leave them fighting an uphill battle all the way. Expect guts and determination but ultimately little in the way of goals or success.</string>
    <string name="prediction27">The Ghana game will be fun, the games against Germany and Portugal will be painful. Group exit.</string>
    <string name="starman27">Making a name for himself at Roma, this industious midfielder is the team\'s stand-out performer.</string>
    <string name="starmanname27">Michael Bradley</string>
    
    <string name="writeup28">With a team-list that belies the diminutive size of their country, Belgium are a team that have a chance to go far in this tournament. Their lack of World Cup experience may play against them but few of the contenders for the title will relish a clash with this capable team.</string>
    <string name="prediction28">Very capable of causing an upset or two. Quarter-finals.</string>
    <string name="starman28">Marshalls the back four and lends composure to all around him, an absolute class act.</string>
    <string name="starmanname28">Vincent Kompany</string>
    
    <string name="writeup29">Having just scraped into the World Cup on away goals, Algeria are the rank outsiders of the tournament. However, with a young team and a strong work ethic, they will be difficult to beat.</string>
    <string name="prediction29">Likely to earn plenty of pride but unlikely to progress from their group.</string>
    <string name="starman29">The Valencia player is the shining performer and Algeria will need him to be at his sparkling best to have a chance of progressing.</string>
    <string name="starmanname29">Sofiane Feghouli</string>
    
    <string name="writeup30">The Russian team is a solid group with a few huge talents, most notably the dangerous Dzagoev. They find themselves in a group they should qualify from and the confidence they gain from that may be a springboard to something greater.</string>
    <string name="prediction30">Second round seems likely, but with likely opponents of Germany or Portugal waiting, that will probably be as far as this team goes.</string>
    <string name="starman30">A lethal finisher, this is a really good chance for the CSKA man to shine under the biggest spotlight.</string>
    <string name="starmanname30">Alan Dzagoev</string>
    
    <string name="writeup31">While they will rarely be outworked, this Korean team looks likely to be outplayed by their more talented group opponents. They won\'t make it easy but I don\'t think they\'ll cause any scares either.</string>
    <string name="prediction31">Won\'t trouble Belgium or Russia. Group exit.</string>
    <string name="starman31">The Leverkusen attacker is the side\'s creative force and their leading light.</string>
    <string name="starmanname31">Son Heung Min</string>

</resources>
